Easy Sage Course Kit
Let's meet up here at 4 PM.
Got ya!
Sorry for being late.
I had trouble with teacher.
I had to finish my homework.
What do you want?
Please tell me...
We're going camping!
What? You all are going camping with Suneo's cousin?
I'll join you guys.
You fool.
You have to do your homework.
Sorry, but I'll be blunt.
Your homework is more important than coming to camp with us.
Dekisugi-san is right. You should reconsider camping with us.
You can't mean that...
What were you doing at this late?
Well, you see...
That's not going to cut it.
You were scolded by your teacher for getting 0, right?
What do you mean?
Oh, the usual?
Not you too, Doraemon.
I want to live on some distant mountain, all by myself.
Wow. You are talking like a sage.
A Sage?
What? You don't know?
Have you ever seen a poster like this?
A sage, huh?
It's an old Chinese legend....
Isolating oneself from the world and live deep in the mountains.
Meditating under waterfall to obtain supernatural powers.
That's almost magical, right?
Well, suppose you can say that...
You seem to know about the magical part of it, huh?
I wanna become a sage too.
I mentioned it as just an old legend, Remember?.
It's impossible for you to beocme a sage.
Say, what's an Easy Sage Course Kit?
Easy Sage
Course Kit
A gadget to become a sage?
Gimme that! i'll be borrowing it!
Are you sure you don't want to do your homework?
Don't come crying to me later, if mum scolds you.
If I become a sage, studying would be like a piece of cake.
You have to undergo harsh practices, you know!
I am ready to undergo even the harshest practices so that...
...I can become a sage!
You're so reckless.
Huh? You won't join me?
But of course. You have to be all alone.
You're so cold! Okay, fine!
I want to go to a snowy mountain with a waterfall.
Wow!
Now let's see what all does this Easy Sage Course Kit contains...
Huh? What's that?
This is an outfit of a sage.
What is this small shrine? It's connected to this air pump.
I see!
So I have to sit inside this shrine and train!
It's finished!
I suppose it's very spacious inside.
Oh, it's so small.
How disappointing.
Who are you? Doll of a Sage?
This idol is my master!
I''m Nobita! Teach me how to become a sage!
Please be easy on me!
I hate difficulty.
You fool!
Is that how you speak to your master?
Ouch! Depsite your small stature, you sure are cocky as hell!
How dare you mock me!
Think you can be swifter than me?
For being just a robot, you're so cocky!
Wait up!
Thunderstorm!
Did you give up?
Please forgive my rudeness.
Alright. Now you can be my disciple.
You mean it? Yay!
First I'll teach you the technique to ride on a cloud.
How do I ride on it?
I mean, how do I ride it, sir?
It's so easy, you just have to stand on it!
Try it! Go ahead!
Normally? Alright, then...
Oh my, what a clumsy disciple!
You have to start your training from the heart.
training from the heart?
First you have to align your heartbeat.
In other words, you have to empty the inside of your heart.
That's so easy!
Your head is so empty
It's not just about the head!
The heart.
Will empty...
You fool, who told you to fall asleep?
Oh, thunderstorm!
I fell asleep while trying to empty my heart.
You have to take the training seriously.
Listen, practice it all alone for a while.
Remember to train!
He's so annoying!
I wonder if Nobita-kun is doing his training properly?
Well, I'll go check on him for once.
I'm surprised to see him like this.
What's this strange doll doing here?
You're so hypocrite, sage. You were the one who told me to be pure hearted.
But you are perverted as always, want to see that too!
See what?
Shizuka-chan's panties.
So you haven't matured spiritually at all yet, have you?